Factors and Factorials 

The factorial of a number N (written N!) is defined as the product of all the integers from 1 to N. It is often defined recursively as follows:

1! = 1 
N! = N ∗ (N −1)! 

Factorials grow very rapidly: 5! = 120, 10! = 3,628,800. One way of specifying such large numbers is by specifying the number of times each prime number occurs in it, thus 825 could be specified as (0 1 2 0 1) meaning no twos, 1 three, 2 fives, no sevens and 1 eleven. 

Write a program that will read in a number N (2 ≤ N ≤ 100) and write out its factorial in terms of the numbers of the primes it contains.

Input:
Input will consist of a series of lines, each line containing a single integer N. The file will be terminated by a line consisting of a single ‘0’.

Output:
Output will consist of a series of blocks of lines, one block for each line of the input. Each block will start with the number N, right justified in a field of width 3, and the characters ‘!’, space, and ‘=’. This will be followed by a list of the number of times each prime number occurs in N!. 
These should be right justified in fields of width 3 and each line (except the last of a block, which may be shorter) should contain fifteen numbers. Any lines after the first should be indented. 
Follow the layout of the example shown below exactly.

Sample Input:
5 
53 
0

Sample Output:
 5! = 3 1 1 
53! = 49 23 12 8 4 4 3 2 2 1 1 1 1 1 1 1